CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.267s | tick 4352 | P06 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.377 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.10 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.333s | tick 4360 | P07 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.162 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.07 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.400s | tick 4368 | P07 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.285 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-49.41 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.467s | tick 4376 | P07 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.285 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.03 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.533s | tick 4384 | P07 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.314 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.34 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.600s | tick 4392 | P08 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.306 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.47 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.667s | tick 4400 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.373 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.33 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.733s | tick 4408 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.299 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.800s | tick 4416 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.222 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.72 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.867s | tick 4424 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.134 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.63 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=36.933s | tick 4432 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.184 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.58 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.000s | tick 4440 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.148 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.60 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.067s | tick 4448 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.146 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.58 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.133s | tick 4456 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.001 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.61 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.200s | tick 4464 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.043 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.65 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.267s | tick 4472 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.070 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.69 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.333s | tick 4480 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.028 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.73 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.400s | tick 4488 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.022 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.78 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.467s | tick 4496 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.85 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.533s | tick 4504 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.016 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.92 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.600s | tick 4512 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.061 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.97 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.667s | tick 4520 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.008 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.733s | tick 4528 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.001 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.01 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.800s | tick 4536 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.000 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.02 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.867s | tick 4544 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.012 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.03 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=37.933s | tick 4552 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.028 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.03 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.000s | tick 4560 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.106 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.067s | tick 4568 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.088 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.97 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.133s | tick 4576 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.022 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.99 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.200s | tick 4584 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.98 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.267s | tick 4592 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.98 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.333s | tick 4600 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.013 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.07 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.400s | tick 4608 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.108 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.01 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.467s | tick 4616 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.017 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.08 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.533s | tick 4624 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-47.76 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.600s | tick 4632 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-43.43 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.667s | tick 4640 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-33.51 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.733s | tick 4648 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-17.52 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.800s | tick 4656 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-2.02 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.867s | tick 4664 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=+8.24 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=38.933s | tick 4672 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=+15.28 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.000s | tick 4680 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=+18.95 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.067s | tick 4688 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=+17.20 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.133s | tick 4696 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=+9.89 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.200s | tick 4704 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.017 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.20 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.267s | tick 4712 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-13.27 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.333s | tick 4720 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-26.24 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.400s | tick 4728 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.017 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-43.38 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.467s | tick 4736 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.173 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.533s | tick 4744 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.109 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.12 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.600s | tick 4752 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.134 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.01 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.667s | tick 4760 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.197 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.64 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.733s | tick 4768 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.019 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.49 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.800s | tick 4776 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.229 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.76 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.867s | tick 4784 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.153 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-51.46 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=39.933s | tick 4792 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.018 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.29 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.000s | tick 4800 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.114 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.13 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.067s | tick 4808 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.186 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.133s | tick 4816 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.031 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.00 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.200s | tick 4824 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.519 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.28 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.267s | tick 4832 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-1.027 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.84 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.333s | tick 4840 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.292 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.64 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.400s | tick 4848 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.430 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.30 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.467s | tick 4856 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.365 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-49.98 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.533s | tick 4864 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.348 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.14 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.600s | tick 4872 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.322 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.36 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.667s | tick 4880 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.419 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-50.25 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.733s | tick 4888 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.591 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-49.59 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.800s | tick 4896 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.375 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-48.35 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.867s | tick 4904 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.348 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-47.22 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=40.933s | tick 4912 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.315 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-46.27 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.000s | tick 4920 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.284 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=FRONT_WALL
RR bottom-to-top gap=-45.32 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.067s | tick 4928 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.375 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-44.31 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.133s | tick 4936 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.310 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-43.27 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.200s | tick 4944 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.250 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-42.29 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.267s | tick 4952 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.293 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-41.34 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.333s | tick 4960 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.288 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-40.35 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.400s | tick 4968 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.293 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-39.36 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.467s | tick 4976 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.329 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-38.28 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.533s | tick 4984 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.347 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-37.30 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.600s | tick 4992 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.350 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-36.24 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.667s | tick 5000 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.335 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-35.12 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.733s | tick 5008 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.362 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-33.87 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.800s | tick 5016 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.343 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-32.64 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.867s | tick 5024 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.401 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-31.41 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=41.933s | tick 5032 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.386 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-30.03 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.000s | tick 5040 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.413 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-28.60 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.067s | tick 5048 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.366 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-27.46 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.133s | tick 5056 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.446 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-26.31 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.200s | tick 5064 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.449 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-25.14 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.267s | tick 5072 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.478 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-23.99 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.333s | tick 5080 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.468 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-22.83 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.400s | tick 5088 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.467 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-21.69 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.467s | tick 5096 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.455 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-20.53 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.533s | tick 5104 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.449 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-19.51 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.600s | tick 5112 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.472 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-18.49 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.667s | tick 5120 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.450 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-17.46 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.733s | tick 5128 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.480 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-16.37 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.800s | tick 5136 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.471 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-15.36 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.867s | tick 5144 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.481 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-14.32 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=42.933s | tick 5152 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.472 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-13.27 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.000s | tick 5160 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.476 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-12.30 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.067s | tick 5168 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.476 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-11.40 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.133s | tick 5176 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.473 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=OBSTACLE_AMBIGUOUS
RR bottom-to-top gap=-10.51 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.200s | tick 5184 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.486 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-9.60 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.267s | tick 5192 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.470 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-8.82 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.333s | tick 5200 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.456 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-8.02 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.400s | tick 5208 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.466 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-7.20 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.467s | tick 5216 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.452 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-6.50 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.533s | tick 5224 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.457 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-5.88 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.600s | tick 5232 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.380 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-5.24 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.667s | tick 5240 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.376 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-4.65 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.733s | tick 5248 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.100 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-4.50 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.800s | tick 5256 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.446 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-4.02 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.867s | tick 5264 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.399 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-3.53 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=43.933s | tick 5272 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.157 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-2.72 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.000s | tick 5280 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.210 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-2.28 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.067s | tick 5288 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.192 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.96 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.133s | tick 5296 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.105 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.77 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.200s | tick 5304 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.260 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.58 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.267s | tick 5312 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.196 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.37 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.333s | tick 5320 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.214 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.21 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.400s | tick 5328 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.079 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.12 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.467s | tick 5336 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.163 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-1.02 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.533s | tick 5344 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.231 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.98 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.600s | tick 5352 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.085 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.93 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.667s | tick 5360 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.092 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.93 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.733s | tick 5368 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.078 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.85 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.800s | tick 5376 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.094 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.85 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.867s | tick 5384 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.101 rad/s | obstacle contact=False | surface=NONE
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.84 mm | air=True | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=44.933s | tick 5392 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.263 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.78 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.000s | tick 5400 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.174 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.68 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.067s | tick 5408 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.244 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.61 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.133s | tick 5416 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.236 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.55 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.200s | tick 5424 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=+0.221 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.53 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.267s | tick 5432 | P09 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.196 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.52 mm | air=False | no new success claim
CP177152 - HISTORICALLY ACCEPTED / RR UNDER REVIEW
1x | source t=45.333s | tick 5440 | P10 | not latest CP177792
RR wheel joint qd=-0.116 rad/s | obstacle contact=True | surface=TOP
RR bottom-to-top gap=-0.49 mm | air=False | no new success claim